relying on something to think for them, right? That's why nature is so great. Go out and spend
three days somewhere in nature. First day, your brain will be all over the place. Second day,
it'll kind of calm down. By the third day, you're like, I'm thinking clearly again because if you
don't have your device and you're looking at the expanse of the sky or mountains or the sea
and you're opening your awareness, your brain gets very organized, right? So a person who
understands that when they go to bed at night, their serotonin levels change to melatonin.
And when you're in serotonin, you're in beta. When you're in melatonin, you start dropping into alpha,
theta and delta. And that's when the door opens. So what do you want to drop in there? Do you want
to do something? Do you want to drop anything in there that's going to cause you to be more
limited or distract you or, you know, cause you to think and feel later on the next day a certain
way? Or do you say, by volition, I'm going to teach my body a motion